<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CDDMA</string>
    <string name="head_title">CDDMA:</string>

    <string name="capture_btn">CAPTURE</string>
    <string name="library_btn">LIBRARY</string>
    <string name="credits_btn">CREDITS</string>

    <string name="credits_text">CREDITS PAGE</string>
    <string name="library_text">LIBRARY PAGE</string>
    <string name="take_pic_txt">Take a photo</string>
    <string name="image_text">Disease Name</string>

    <string name="title_activity_library">Library</string>
    <string name="title_activity_credits">Credits</string>
    <string name="title_activity_display">Display Image</string>
    <string name="title_activity_capture_img">Capture Image</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_screen">SplashScreen</string>

    <string name="toggle_camera">Toggle Camera</string>
    <string name="detect_object">Detect</string>
    <string name="info_btn">Info</string>
    <string name="send_btn">Send Message</string>

    <string name="mobile_num">Mobile#</string>

    <string name="epD"><b>EcotoPatasites</b>
        \nFive species of louse infest cattle: the biting or chewing louse
    </string>
    <string name="epT"><b>Treatment</b>
        \nUse a pour-on synthetic pyrethroid preparation such as deitamerthrin
    </string>
    <string name="epP"><b>Prevention</b>
        \nAll cattle in direct contact must be treated
    </string>

    <string name="wrD"><b>Warts</b>
        \nCattle warts are caused by an infectious and contagious virus
        (bovine papilloma virus; BPV) that spreads via contact from infected
        cattle to non-infected cattle
    </string>
    <string name="wrT"><b>Treatment</b>
        \nIsolate affected cattle to reduce the chance of spread.
        Warts can be removed surgically, or by tying a tight ligature
        around the base, depending on the number, type, size and locations.
    </string>
    <string name="wrP"><b>Prevention</b>
        \nIsolate affected cattle to reduce the chance of spread
    </string>

    <string name="lsD"><b>Lumpy Skin</b>
        \nLumpy skin disease is an infectious disease in cattle caused by a virus of the family Poxviridae, also known as Neethling virus
    </string>
    <string name="lsT"><b>Treatment</b>
        \nThere is no treatment for the virus, so prevention by vaccination is the most effective means of control
    </string>
    <string name="lsP"><b>Prevention</b>
        \nVaccination is the most effective means of control, and live homologous vaccines containing a Neethling-like strain of LSDV are recommended
    </string>


    <string name="peD"><b>Pink Eye</b>
        \nPinkeye, also known as infectious bovine keratoconjunctivitis (IBK),
        is one of the most common diseases of beef cattle in Virginia.
        It is a highly contagious disease, causing inflammation of the
        cornea (the clear outer layer) and conjunctiva (the pink membrane
        lining the eyelids) of the eye
    </string>
    <string name="peT"><b>Treatment</b>
        \nFly control using ear tags and pour-on insecticides is never absolute and repeated treatments prove costly
    </string>
    <string name="peP"><b>Prevention</b>
        \nOutbreaks of IBK may occur after the introduction of purchased stock therefore, whenever possible, all new stock should be managed separately as one group away from the main herd
    </string>

    <string name="lmD"><b>Lameness</b>
        \nThe best all-encompassing definition of lameness includes any abnormality which causes a cow to change the way that she walks, and can be caused by a range of foot and leg conditions, themselves caused by disease, management or environmental factors
    </string>
    <string name="lmT"><b>Treatment</b>
        \nDutch 5 step claw trimming - steps 1-3 correct claw shape and confirm the sole ulcer.Anti-inflammatory drugs
    </string>
    <string name="lmP"><b>Prevention</b>
        \nGood nutrition is fundamentally important for the general health and productivity of dairy cows. However, there are no proven direct links with acidosis or laminitis.
        Therefore, methods for reducing sole ulcers by altering diets alone, should focus on minimising body condition score loss.
        Other preventative measures include reducing standing on concrete, particularly at calving
    </string>

    <string name="credits_txt">Ager Novus would like to thank the following that helps us develop,
        validate and certified the CDDMA: Cow Diseases Detector for Mobile Application."</string>
    <string name="credits_txt2">Dairy Farms and Offices:
        \n- Luzon Dairy Cooperative
        \n- ARB Livestock
        \n- Mateo Cow and Calf Farms
        \n- City Veterinary Office (SJDM Branch)
        \n- Municipality of San Jose Del Monte Bulacan</string>
    <string name="credits_txt3">Veterinarians and Livestock Owners:
        \n- Dr. Arvin Agapito
        \n- Dr. Jayson Perez
        \n- Dr. Rhommel Mendoza
        \n- Dr. Jose Restituto De Ocampo
        \n- Dr. Arby Banaa
        \n- Mr. Allan Ray Baluyut
        \n- Mr. Kiel Victor Mateo
        \n- Mr. Andy Hilario</string>
    <string name="credits_txt4">Contacts:
        \n- Dr. Arvin Agapito   (09178025162/arvinagapito82@yahoo.com)
        \n- Dr. Jayson Perez    (096550421936/jayson.perez@gmail.com.ph)
        \n- Allan Ray Baluyut   (09178353721/konsi_arb@yahoo.com.ph)
        \n- Kiel Victor Matero (09178938038)</string>
    <string name="credits_txt5">Developers/Researchers:
        \n- Allen Dale D. Baluyut
        \n- Dan Elijah B. Inocentes
        \n- Roy Ruiz Rogero
        \n- Armin Carl E. Valdez</string>


</resources>
